She hid in a different
syndicate.
It seems we have no other choice
but to break into that
Godfather's villa.
I'd like to ask
for your husband's help.
One of my employees,
her husband, is in jail.
His name is former
Major Miguel Delgado.
I'll try to see what I can do.
Do you know Vicente Alcala's
house?
The events team sent me
for his party.
Joey, you're not included.
It's not good when there's
a woman.
You might get emotional again.
What's your real issue with me?
Is it because I'm a failure,
or because I'm emotional?
Or because I'm a woman?
Maybe she'll find out something
about the organization.
Should I work on it?
No, as long as she doesn't know,
we can use her against
his husband.
And that's how we burn him
slowly.
By the way, can I ask you
for a favor?
It's not because you're a police
officer outside,
you're important here.
Andrew, join us!
Alcohol is dangerous for robots
because they'll get rusty,
and they'll lose feelings
even more.
Game.
Give me that.
Why? What do you think?
I can't drink because
I'm a woman, right?
- Shot! Shot!
- Just take it easy.
That's enough, you're drunk.
What do I need to do so you
don't treat me like a child?
Tell me!
What is this?
What are you doing to Joey?
You animal!
You're taking advantage of her
because she's drunk!
- Wait.
- What's your problem?
You got it wrong.
I don't have a problem.
Then explain.
Why are you on top of her?
She pulled me.
I fell on her.
That's it. Accident.
Is that true? Is that true,
Joey?
True.
Joey...
Did you kiss her?
Me?
Paranoid.
Wanna drink some more?
Okay.
You're drunk!
You've outdone the guys bumming
around in our area.
Have some water.
Am I really a failure, Peter?
What? No!
Don't believe Andrew.
Boss Budol is his name,
that's why he's like that!
Don't believe that, don't.
- Never, never. Never say...
- Boss Budol.
You called him that.
What?
Boss Budol...
- Boss Budol...
- You know...
You're really my best friend.
Thank you.
At least, you, you know
I'm not a failure.
- Right?
- No. You're not a failure.
You're not a failure.
You're so good.
You're so brave.
You're even braver than me.
You know that?
That's why we're not the same.
You're here! This is you,
and this is me.
There you are.
Tall.
My height.
But you know,
even though we're different,
I won't give up. No!
Because...
nothing, that's how it is...
I love you.
I have a chance, don't I?
Buddy, a letter?
A letter to my family.
But I never sent it.
They changed their address.
I don't know how to find them.
I know I don't value here,
but I have a lot of connections
outside.
I can make them find
your family.
What do you need from Trigger?
Are you going to ask for help?
He's cunning
and a double-crosser.
I just need some information
from him.
Maybe...
angels are good at pretending
to be demons like him.
But those guys have weaknesses,
too.
Don't.
Let's drink more.
More shots.
That's enough.
We're out of alcohol.
You're not allowed
to drink anymore.
Am I not allowed?
Why am I not allowed?
Are you the boss?
Yes, and, I'm ordering you
to go to sleep.
I don't want to!
You're arrogant. You're perfect.
Really?
You're perfect.
Hardworking.
Brave.
Handsome.
I'm handsome?
Yes...
Boss Idol, right?
That's why...
That's why what?
Okay.
Hon, what will I say
to Clarissa?
You know, something that could
give her hope.
I already talked to a friend
at the RTC.
The case is serious.
Murder, non-bailable.
But they say they can consider
a motion for reconsideration
of bail.
Especially if there
are lapses in evidence or,
mitigating factors.
Thank you, Hon.
But I hope, don't think
I'm just using you.
Too late.
Almost there.
But you know, Hon,
seriously, I just feel
for Clarissa.
She's kind, and honestly,
it's a shame because she's smart
and competent.
If she weren't going through
something
so difficult in her life,
I know...
I know she could do more.
That's why I want to meet her.
I want to hear her story
firsthand,
so we know what and who we're
letting ourselves in for.
Okay, okay, I'll set it up,
okay?
Thank you.
- Joey, you eat first, so...
- No need, Peter. I'll do it.
I can do it.
Just because I'm a girl,
I'm all emotions, right?
You want water, Joey?
Thank you, Jin Ho.
You're so sweet.
You really care
about my feelings.
You should analyze the situation
first before you say anything.
It's more important to analyze
your egos first.
So...
so I have issues with my ego?
Why? Did it affect you?
Just wait.
There will come a moment,
a crack in the wall,
a look, then you'll suddenly
realize...
why does this girl matter a lot?
Here.
What's this?
Coconut water for hydration
and hangover.
So you don't look like a zombie
all day.
Water first.
Thank you.
My head hurts.
What happened last night?
I blacked out.
Don't you remember
what I said to you?
What did you say?
I don't remember what I said.
I guess it's not important.
It's just nothing.
- What is it?
- Drink it.
Maybe...
Maybe you'll remember.
So you don't remember what you
said to me last night either?
I don't remember anything.
What did I say?
I said nothing.
How sure are you
that you'll find my family?
Even though I'm no longer
in the service,
I still have a lot
of connections.
My fellow cops,
government people, politicians,
even criminals.
I've talked to Trigger.
He agreed to what you wanted.
Hey!
Let's move to Building A!
Let's talk later.
So later, I will head out.
I will try to get access
to their office
and find the guest list.
And I can do it on my own.
I don't need a chaperone.
Okay, just make sure that
my name is on that list.
Didn't we talk about this, Joey?
- You're not coming.
- And why?
Did I agree to what you wanted?
What?
You're having trouble with me
being a woman again, aren't you?
There we go.
Please, Andrew, I can fight too.
I'm a black belter.
Okay.
Thank you for agreeing
to talk to me.
I just wanted to...
I don't want trouble.
I just want to know something.
What if you betray me like what
you did to your best friend,
Major Aglipay?
I'm not his traitor.
He betrayed me,
that's why I'm locked up here.
I'm not part of their syndicate.
And you're fooling me, right?
Open this door!
Hey, what are you doing there?
Back to the cell.
You're lucky now.
Clarissa...
Yes?
I have good news for you.
I've already talked
to my husband
about your husband's case.
Really?
Yes, but he wants to know more,
that's why he wants to talk
to you.
But he's just in Hong Kong
for a conference.
But when he arrives,
I'll introduce you to him.
Okay, Ma'am.
Thank you very much, Ma'am.
I don't know how to repay you.
Of course, we help each other
here.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
An invitation has arrived
from one of our target sponsors.
It's such short notice.
Should I decline?
Well, I hope Tomas is here.
It's more strategic that way,
right?
Yes.
Ma'am, excuse me.
Well, it would be a waste
of an opportunity
if you don't go for it.
Also, we've been courting
that sponsor for a long time.
Well, you're right.
We cannot miss this opportunity,
right?
Okay.
Confirm my attendance, okay?
- Okay, Ma'am.
- Thank you.
Joey, you don't have
to do this anymore.
I need to, so we'll finally
know.
This is in your favor!
The area is wide enough
and if you get tired,
you can run, right?
Can you hear what she says?
You're laughing there.
You go first, so your giggles
will disappear!
Let's go, Brother!
- Don't, don't.
- You're so weak!
- Just stand there!
- I'm not yet ready.
- Let's go! I'll help you.
- Yes, I'll do it.
I got you.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Joey, does being a black belter
help you with this?
Remember.
Your enemies are gun smugglers.
And check again.
Your turn.
Keep going.
Good job!
Wow Joey. You're fast.
Maybe you've forgotten that
my father is a police officer?
But we'll only use that when
were at a disadvantage.
It's always good to be ready.
And it's even better
if you can shoot.
Okay, Joey, game.
Okay...
One foot forward for balance.
Bend your knees.
Firm grip.
Firm.
Don't lock your elbows.
Eyes up.
Breathe.
Steady.
Game, you can do it.
Joey, control that...
Control this.
Don't jerk...
and keep aiming after every
shot.
Go, Joey. You can do it!
It's my hair.
Give me that.
Joey, this is...
Not bad.
Five, why...
How did you do that?
Expert....
Joey, can we talk?
Braganza has a target here
in Luzon.
We need to find out what
they're up to, Matias.
It looks like the transaction
will happen there.
Golda.
Long live the king!
Has my gift arrived yet?
Joey, be careful.
If something goes wrong,
just walk away.